[

    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "How is the number 9 represented as a binary number?",
    correct_answer: "1001",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "1000",
    "1110",
    "1010"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "In Roman Numerals, what does XL equate to?",
    correct_answer: "40",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "60",
    "15",
    "90"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "What&#039;s the square root of 49?",
    correct_answer: "7",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "4",
    "12",
    "9"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "boolean",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.",
    correct_answer: "False",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "What is the symbol for Displacement?",
    correct_answer: "&Delta;r",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "dr",
    "Dp",
    "r"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "The metric prefix &quot;atto-&quot; makes a measurement how much smaller than the base unit?",
    correct_answer: "One Quintillionth",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "One Billionth",
    "One Quadrillionth",
    "One Septillionth"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "boolean",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.",
    correct_answer: "True",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "boolean",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "A scalene triangle has two sides of equal length.",
    correct_answer: "False",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "True"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "boolean",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "An equilateral triangle always has every angle measuring 60&deg;.",
    correct_answer: "True",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "False"
    ]
    },
    {
    category: "Science: Mathematics",
    type: "multiple",
    difficulty: "easy",
    question: "How many sides does a trapezium have?",
    correct_answer: "4",
    incorrect_answers: [
    "3",
    "5",
    "6"
    ]
    }
    
    ]